添加支持位置的插入，看起来
Adding support for the location insert, looks almost
和添加支持天气差不多，我们只要
identical to adding support for weather. We just have
选择正确的表名，并且
to select the right table name, and return
返回正确的位置URI就可以。但是，还有一件事情要做
the right location URI. But there's one more thing
我们要做的就是
to do. All we have to do is
为这个函数中传入的URI调用
call getContext().getContentResolver().notifyChange on the
getContext().getContentResolver().notifyChange
URI that was actually passed
来通知任何需要知道的观察者
into our function. To notify any observers that need
UI已经改变了
to know that UI has changed. And that's it.
我们现在已经完成插入了，然而
We've now finished insert. However, of course,
我们要添加一个测试才能真正的完成它
we're never done without also adding a test.